Finding Aid for Vice President for Student Affairs (University of Michigan) Records
Bentley Historical Library
- Henry Johnson, Vice-President of Student Services, 1950-1985; 1972-1985
  - Topical Files
    - Housing
      - Off Campus Housing, 1968-1988 (Box 24)
      - Off Campus Mediation Services, 1970; 1972 (Box 24)
      - Organizational Chart, 1972 (Box 24)
      - Policy Committee Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
      - Price, Melvia Miller, 1985 (Box 36)
        [Student records restricted until July 01, 2070 ]
        (investigative case)
      - Program Evaluation Committee, 1978 (Box 24)
      - Project Awareness Proposal, 1972 (Box 24)
      - Rates, Residence Hall and Family Housing, 1975-1989 (Box 24)
      - Recycling/Waste Management, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
      - Reports, 3 folders
        - Demographic and Lifestyle Research Report, undated (Box 25)
        - Family Housing Community Services Status Report, 1982-1983; 1983 (Box 25)
        - Family Housing Rate Committee Report, 1980 (Box 25)
        - Family Housing Rate Study Committee Final Report, 1990 (Box 25)
        - Family Housing Rate Study Committee Report, 1982 (Box 25)
        - Family Housing Rate Study Committee, 1975-76 (Box 25)
        - Family Housing-Community Center Survey, 1980 (Box 25)
        - Family Housing-Exit Survey, 1989 (Box 25)
        - Minority Student Recruitment and Retention, 1982-1983 (Box 25)
        - Proposed Family/Married Housing Rates for, 1978-1979; 1978 (Box 25)
        - Report of the Rate Study Committee 1975-76 (Box 25)
        - Single Student Housing Rate Study Committee Report, 1989-1990 (Box 25)
        - Single Student Rate Study Committee Report, 1981-1982 (Box 25)
        - Student Housing at the University of Michigan:, 1969; 1971 (Box 25)
        - Student Housing, Report of the President's Off-Campus Housing Commission, 1965 (Box 25)
        - Study Locations and Grades, 1985 (Box 25)
        - Studying in Residence Halls, 1985 (Box 25)
        - Task Force on Alcohol, 1986 (Box 25)
        - The Black Experience & U. of M. Residence Halls, 1968-1977; 1978 (Box 25)
      - Residence, Type of (includes Percentage of Students by Type of Residence, 1949-1985), 1970-1989 (Box 25)
      - Residence Diversity Education, 1987 (Box 25)
      - Residence Hall Association (RHA) (minutes), 1985 (Box 25)
      - Residency Hall Judiciary Councils, 1967 (Box 25)
      - Security Reports (monthly), 1983-1989; 4 folders (Box 25)
      - Small Group Housing, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
      - Staff Manual, 1974; 1978; 1984 (Box 25)
      - Staff Review (assessment of Housing Division), 1981 (Box 25)
      - Student Survey (re: residence hall living), 1972 (Box 25)
      - Unit Committee Minutes, 1971-1975; 2 folders (Box 25)
      - University Terrace, 1986-1989 (Box 25)
    - Institute for Administrative Advancement, undated (Box 25)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics, Dept. of (review of), 1987 (Box 25)
    - Intercooperative Council, 1960-1971 (Box 25)
    - International Center
      - General, 1965-1989; 6 folders (Box 25)
      - Banana Club, 1971 (Box 26)
      - Budget, 1971-1974 (Box 26)
      - Cross Cultural Adjustment Simulation Game, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
      - Dotson Report (re: foreign student advisors), 1972 (Box 26)
      - Foreign Students
        - Enrollment, 1969-1973 (Box 26)
        - Orientation, 1970-1973 (Box 26)
        - Scholarships, 1967-1970 (Box 26)
      - German Exchange Program, 1974 (Box 26)
      - Grant Proposals, 1975-1989 (Box 26)
      - Immigration Regulations, 1983 (Box 26)
      - Objectives/Reorganization, 1972 (Box 26)
      - Policy Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 26)
      - Reports
        - An Investigation of Friendship Patterns of Foreign Students, 1968 (Box 26)
        - Community Services to Foreign Students, 1966 (Box 26)
        - Foreign Student Survey 1964-65, Summary of General Findings, circa 1966 (Box 26)
        - International Student Needs Assessment, 1984 (Box 26)
      - Program Proposals, 1972 (Box 26)
      - Special Interest Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 26)
      - Staff Meetings (minutes), 1972 (Box 26)
      - Wagner Scholarship Fund, 1962-1969 (Box 26)
      - Work Study/Travel Abroad, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
    - International Neighbors, 1972; 1974 (Box 26)
    - International Student Program Development Conference, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Jazz For Life (Arts for Life), 1986 (Box 26)
    - Johnson, Henry
      - Correspondence, 1972-1989; 10 folders (Box 26)
      - Speeches, Miscellaneous Writings & Background Information (bulk 1987), 1975-1988 (Box 26)
    - Joint Conference Commission, 1965-1973; 2 folders (Box 26)
      (mostly minutes; folder 1 contains background information
    - Joint Judiciary Council (Box 27)
      - General, 1960-1969; 2 folders (Box 27)
        (folder 1 includes constitution and by-laws)
    - Petitions for Membership, 1967-1968
      - Residence Hall Judiciary Structure Survey, 1966 (Box 27)
      - Violations, 1966-1968 (Box 36)
        [Student records restricted until July 01, 2053 ]
    - Latin American Conference, undated (Box 27)
    - Legal Services, Student
      - General, 1975-1985; 4 folders (Box 27)
      - Audit Reports, 1979-1989 (scattered) (Box 27)
      - Demographic Reports, 1979-1985; 7 folders (Box 27)
      - History and Background Information, 1979-1985 (Box 27)
      - Participation Reports, 1979-1985; 1984-1985 (monthly) (Box 27)
    - Leonard Greenbaum Recognition Award, 1984 (Box 27)
    - Lesbian-Gay Male Programs Office
      - General, 1971-1974; 1985-1989; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 27)
      - Report to the Vice President, 1988 (Box 27)
      - Reports
        - Rapping (Evaluative Research of the Gay Rap Program), 1986 (Box 27)
      - Statistical Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 27)
    - Living Learning Committee
      - General (includes minutes), 1971-1972 (Box 27)
      - Pilot Program, 1971-1973 (Box 27)
      - Pilot Curriculum Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 27)
      - Reports
        - Report of the Living Learning Committee, 1973 (Box 27)
    - Madelon Pound House Child Care Center
      - General, 1975-1977; 1987-1989; 2 folders (Box 27)
        (includes board meeting minutes)
      - Development of, 1973 (Box 27)
      - Proposal for Early Childhood Center, 1975 (Box 27)
    - Major Events, Office of (Box 28)
      - General, 1981-1989; 1982-1985 (Box 28)
      - Year End Report, 1984-1985 (Box 28)
    - Management by Objectives, 1974-1976 (Box 28)
    - Martin Luther King Day, 1989-1990 (Box 28)
      (See Also-Diversity)
    - Measles Immunization Policy, 1985-1986 (Box 28)
    - Mediation Services
      - General, 1971-1978 (Box 28)
      - Purpose, 1972 (Box 28)
      - Statistical Report (monthly), 1987 (Box 28)
    - Michigamua (re: Native American racial harassment), 1989 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Collegiate Coalition, 1988-1989 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Daily, 1985 (Box 28)
    - Michigan League
      - Board of Governors, 1967-1980 (Box 28)
      - Manual for Board Members, 1967 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Mandate, 1989 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Stadium Policy (re: carry-in & pass-out policy), 1989 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Student Assembly
      - General, 1976-1989; 9 folders (Box 28)
      - Committee on Referral, 1960; 1966 (Box 28)
      - Constitution, 1986 (Box 28)
      - Fee Assessment Requests, 1983-1990; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Meeting Procedures, circa 1982 (Box 28)
      - Minutes, 1977-1978; 1980-1984; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Reports
        - A Report of the Recruitment, Retention and Graduation Project of the MSA, 1985 (Box 28)
        - Committee on Reorganization Summary Report to the Michigan Student Assembly, 1985 (Box 28)
        - Consumer Report #1: A Study of Personal Article Prices in the Central Campus Area, 1969 (Box 28)
        - Military Research at Michigan-Roger Kerson, 1983 (Box 28)
        - Student Government Council Opinion of the Report of the Special Study Committee for the Office of Student Affairs, 1962 (Box 28)
        - The University of Michigan Budget-A Report to the Michigan Student Assembly, 1983 (Box 28)
      - Student Government Council (Box 29)
        - General, 1966-1974 (Box 29)
        - Guidelines Being Surveyed, 1974 (Box 29)
        - Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 29)
        - Student Organizations Board, 1974 (Box 29)
      - Student Organizations (recognized), 1983-1989 (Box 29)
        (See Also-Organizational Services)
      - Student Survey, 1987-1989 (Box 29)
      - Women's Issues Committee, 1986 (Box 29)
    - Michigan Union
      - General, 1973-1989; 4 folders (Box 29)
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1970-1979 (Box 29)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1966; 1972 (Box 29)
      - Goals, 1985 (Box 29)
      - Grant Proposal (Arts En-Compass), 1989 (Box 29)
      - Interim Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box 29)
      - Report to the Vice President, 1984-1986 (Box 29)
      - Reports
        - Report of the Michigan Union 1978 (Box 29)
        - Report to the Regents of the University of Michigan, 1989 (Box 29)
      - Space Usage, 1978-1986 (Box 29)
        (See Also-Special Services & Programs, Office Of)
      - Surveys (opinion and marketing), circa 1979 (Box 29)
      - Union Review Committee (minutes), 1978 (Box 29)
    - Michigan Vice Presidents and Deans of Student Affairs (state-wide, includes some minutes), 1983-1989 (Box 29)
    - Midwest Deans Conference, 1972-1986 (Box 29)
    - Minority Affairs, Office of
      - General, 1975-1989; 4 folders (Box 29)
        (f(older 3 contains listing of support services and programs))
      - Ethnic and Minority Funding, 1979 (Box 29)
      - Moody, Charles (Vice Provost), 1987-1988 (Box 29)
        (includes Brief Progress Report on Minority Affairs Agenda, 5-2-88)
      - Proposal for the Improvement of Minority Student Services (Box 29)
      - Rainbow Planning Session, 1989 (Box 29)
    - Minority Students
      - African American
        - General, 1972-1976 (Box 29)
        - Black Student Advocate, 1972-1974 (Box 29)
        - Luncheon, 1986 (Box 30)
        - Summer Orientation, 1975 (Box 30)
      - Asian Americans, 1981-1989 (Box 30)
      - Chicano Americans
        - General, 1971-1985 (Box 30)
        - Advocate/Liaison, 1972-1974 (Box 30)
      - Enrollment, 1973-1989; 3 folders
        (folder 3 includes list of 86/87 honor recipients)
      - Hispanic Americans
        - General, 1981-1987 (Box 30)
        - Leadership Conference, 1989 (Box 30)
        - Lecture Series, 1980 (Box 30)
      - Iranian Students, 1978-1981 (Box 30)
      - Jewish Student Concerns, 1972-1989 (Box 30)
      - Latino Students, 1976-1989 (Box 30)
      - Minority Enrollment Meeting, 1973 (Box 30)
      - Native American Students
        - General, 1971-1986 (Box 30)
        - Advocate
          - General, 1973-74 (Box 30)
          - Annual Report, 1973 (Box 30)
      - Nigerian Students, 1983 (Box 30)
      - Organizations, undated-See Also-Michigan Student Assembly (Box 30)
      - Orientation/Welcome, 1984; 1986 (Box 30)
      - Reports
        - Minority Students at the University of Michigan: 83-84, 1984 (Box 30)
        - Report of the Task Force on Minority Student Concerns, 1981 (Box 30)
        - The Black Student Lounge, 1989 (Box 30)
        - The Relationship Between the Financial Aids Office and Underprivileged African Americans, 1968 (Box 30)
      - Zionist Students
        - Concerns, 1977 (Box 30)
        - Grievances, 1989 (Box 36)
    - NAACP (re: Meeting with President Shapiro), 1987 (Box 30)
    - National Association of State University Land Grant Colleges Council (NASULGC), 1987-1989 (Box 30)
    - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (NASPA), 1988-1989 (Box 30)
    - Needs Assessment Coordinating Committee minutes, 1974-1978 (Box 30)
    - Nite Owl Bus Service, 1986 (Box 30)
      (See Also-Bus Service)
    - Non-Academic Career Counseling and Placement for Graduate Students, Office of
      - Goals and Objectives, 1976 (Box 30)
      - Report
        - A Study of Employment Skills Among American Studies Graduate Students, circa 1979 (Box 30)
    - North Campus Commons, 1988-1989 (Box 30)
    - North Campus Impact Study (re: engineering school), 1982 (Box 30)
    - Ombudsman, Office of
      - General, 1977-1989 (Box 30)
      - Goals and Objectives, 1971-1989 (scattered dates) (Box 30)
      - Grievances, 1978-1987 (Box 36)
      - Monthly Reports, 1984-1989 (Box 30)
    - Operation Crossroads Africa, 1979-1982 (Box 30)
    - Opportunity Award Program, 1973 (Box 30)
    - Opportunity Program, 1972; 1980-1983 (Box 30)
    - Organizational Services
      - General Information, 1971-1974; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Budget, 1970-1973 (Box 30)
      - The First Resort-Index, (resource book for organizations), 1972 (Box 30)
      - Organizational Psychology Program, 1972-1973 (Box 30)
      - Report to the Vice President, 1970; 1972 (Box 30)
      - Sports Clubs Funding, 1972 (Box 30)
      - Student Organization List, 1971 (Box 30)
        (See Also-Michigan Student Assembly)
      - Political Groups Usage, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Orientation, Office of, 1971-1989 (Box 31)
      (See Also-Minority Students)
    - Ostafin, Peter (Associate Director of Housing Division), 1983-1984 (Box 31)
    - Panhellenic, 1977-1990 (Box 31)
    - Part-Time Enrollment, 1982 (Box 31)
    - Passing-Up (re: U of M football games), 1980-1981 (Box 31)
    - Peace Corps Anniversary, 1980 (Box 31)
    - Peace Studies Committee, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Pelz, Donald
      (See Also-Housing-Reports)
      - 1969 Summer School Population Needs Survey, 1970 (Box 31)
      - Survey of Student Services, 1973 (Box 31)
    - Pendleton Arts Information Center, 1971-1974 (Box 31)
    - Presidents Council, 1987-1989 (Box 31)
    - Program Analysis, Office of, 1977-1986 (Box 31)
    - Project Community
      - General, 1971-1989; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Black Community Projects Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 31)
      - Career Information and Counseling Center for Black Youth, 1971 (Box 31)
      - Constitution, 1971 (Box 31)
      - Elderly Service Corps, 1989 (Box 31)
      - Final Evaluation, 1974 (Box 31)
      - Innovative Tutorial Experience, 1972-1973 (Box 31)
      - Matrix, 1972 (Box 31)
      - Project Serve, 1989 (Box 31)
      - T-LC Mentoring Project, 1989 (Box 31)
      - Trained Volunteer Corps (T.V.C.), 1989 (Box 31)
    - Psychiatric Emergency Assistance Coordination Effort (PEACE) Task Force (includes minutes), 1978-1980 (Box 31)
    - Psychopharmacological Clinic, 1986-1988 (Box 31)
    - Public Interest Research Group in Michigan (PIRGIM)
      - General, 1975-1987; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Report
        - PIRGIM-Women's Safety Task Force Committee on Security: Report of Its Findings, 1984 (Box 31)
    - Public Service Intern Program, 1982-1984 (Box 31)
    - Quality of Student Life (re: presentation to executive officers), 1982-1986 (Box 31)
    - Racism See Also-Discrimination
      - Concerns, 1986-1987 (Box 31)
      - Won Case, 1987 (Box 36)
    - Rackham Student Government Fee, 1979 (Box 31)
    - Regents (re: student services by-law and policy changes), 1985 (Box 31)
    - Research and Development Committee, 1974 (Box 31)
    - Residential College- Between Two Worlds, The Residential College at the University of Michigan, 1980 (Box 31)
    - Robinson, Barbara-Black/Afro American Representative, 1988 (Box 31)
    - Safe Passage Committee, 1985 (Box 31)
    - Safety and Security, 1987-1989 (Box 31)
    - Satoh Harassment Incident, 1987 (Box 36)
    - School and College Government Funding Proposal, 1971 (Box 31)
    - Senior Swing-Out (includes history), 1984-1989 (Box 31)
    - Sexual Assault Prevention and Awareness Center (SAPAC)
      - General, 1980-1989; 3 folders (Box 32)
      - Budget, 1989 (Box 32)
      - Clinical Statistics, 1988 (Box 32)
      - Peer Program
        - Applications
          - Acceptances, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
          - Acceptances (wait list), 1986-1987 (Box 32)
          - Rejections, 1986-1987 (Box 32)
        - Facilitators Certificates, undated (Box 32)
      - Report to the Vice President, 1989 (Box 32)
      - Search Committee (for center coordinator), 1985 (Box 32)
    - Sexual Discrimination
      (See Also-Discrimination)
      - General, 1985-1987 (Box 32)
      - Policy Statement (U of M), 1980 (Box 32)
      - Proposed By-Law, 1971-1973 (Box 32)
      - Report
        - Report on the Handling of Sexual Harassment Matters at the University of Michigan, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Sexual Orientation
      - General, 1973-1985 (Box 32)
      - Report
        - A Report on Discrimination on the Basis of Sexual Orientation, 1983 (Box 32)
    - South Africa, 1979-1988 (Box 32)
    - Space Needs, 1973 (Box 32)
      (See Also-Michigan Union)
    - Special Services & Programs, Office of
      - Advertising Information Center (AIC)
        - General, 1970-1972 (Box 32)
        - Policies and Procedures, 1971-1972 (Box 32)
      - Affirmative Action, 1973-1974 (Box 32)
      - All Campus Calendar, 1972 (Box 32)
      - Budget Priorities and Proposals, 1972-1974 (Box 32)
      - Commission on Student Governance, 1973 (Box 32)
      - Education Innovation Advocate, 1972-1974 (Box 32)
      - Family Advocate, 1972 (Box 32)
      - Michigan Advertising Works (MAWS), 1974 (Box 32)
      - Publication Materials, 1974 (Box 32)
      - School and College Government Advocate, 1972 (Box 32)
      - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1972-1974 (Box 32)
      - Use of University Facilities, 1972-1974 (Box 32)
        (See Also-Space Needs)
      - Veterans Advocate, 1971-1972 (Box 32)
    - Speech Clinic, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Sports Clubs, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Standard Practice Guide, 1973-1974 (Box 32)
    - Student Auditor's Office (re: student organizations), 1965-1977 (Box 32)
    - Student Awareness Project (student to student communications link), 1982 (Box 32)
    - Student Code, 1982-1984; 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Student Conduct-Interim Disciplinary Rules, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Student Committees- Report of Student Influence at the University of Michigan and Some Directions for Change, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Student Data Service, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
    - Student Fee Allocation, 1971 (Box 32)
    - Student Information Services (SIS) (budget information), 1989-1990 (Box 32)
    - Student Mental Health, 1986-1988 (Box 33)
    - Student Organization Development Center (SODC)
      - General, 1985-1989 (Box 33)
      - Leadership Conference, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Student Organizational Services
      - General, 1969-1974 (Box 33)
      - Report
        - The Joint Task Force on Legal Issues in Student Activities, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Student Organizations, Activities & Programs Office, (SOAP), 1983-1984 (Box 33)
    - Student Programs, Office of (annual reports), 1975-1978 (Box 33)
    - Student Theater Arts Complex, 1979 (Box 33)
    - Student Records
      - Committee, 1973 (Box 33)
      - Hearing Procedures, 1973-1975 (Box 33)
      - Policies On, 1977 (Box 33)
    - Student Recognition/Achievement Awards (lists of recipients), 1983-1989 (Box 33)
    - Student Services, Office of
      - General, 1973-1987 (Box 33)
      - Affirmative Action, 1984-1985 (Box 33)
      - Area Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 33)
      - Auxiliary Meeting (with Vice President and Chief Financial Officer Womack), 1989 (Box 33)
      - Budget Information, 1972-1977; 1985-1989; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Calendaring Committee, 1972 (Box 33)
      - Committee to Study Advocacy, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
      - Communications Task Force (re: in-house publications), 1971-1974 (Box 33)
      - Coordinator for Women, 1971-1972 (Box 33)
        (See Also-Women)
      - Directors' Meetings agendas and minutes, 1968-1989; 7 folders (Box 33)
      - Directors' Retreat, 1976-1987 (scattered dates) (Box 33)
      - Diversity Initiatives, 1987 (Box 33)
      - Goals and Objectives, 1970-1986 (Box 33)
      - Handicapped Students, 1968; 1971 (Box 33)
        (See Also-Disabled Students)
      - Historical Information, 1954-1984 (Box 33)
      - In-Service Training, 1977 (Box 33)
      - Internship Programs, 1974 (Box 33)
      - Minority Employment Goals, 1969 (Box 33)
      - Orientation Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 33)
      - Policy Board, 1967-1976; 4 folders (Box 33)
      - Program Evaluation Committee (PEC), 1978-1979 (Box 34)
      - Reorganization, 1971 (Box 34)
      - Reports, 3 folders
        - American Corporations and Racial Discrimination in South Africa, 1972 (Box 34)
        - Institutional Response: The U-M Office of Student Services to, 1970; 1974 undated (Box 34)
        - Model Policies Governing Student Records: A Minority Report, 1968 (Box 34)
        - Needs as a Guide Toward Priorities, undated (Box 34)
        - Policies Governing Student Records: Majority Report, 1968 (Box 34)
        - Recommendations for Sex Education at the University of Michigan, 1968 (Box 34)
        - Report of the Committee to Study Advocacy at the University of Michigan, 1975 (Box 34)
        - Report of The Special Study Committee for the Office of Student Affairs, 1962 (Box 34)
        - Student Perceptions of the University, 1983 (Box 34)
      - Sex Education Committee, minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 34)
      - Social Work, School of- Study of Women Students at the University of Michigan, 1975 (Box 34)
      - Staff Development Committee, 1988 (Box 34)
      - Staff Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 34)
      - Strategic Planning Retreat, 1989 (Box 34)
      - Student Record Subcommittee, 1973 (Box 34)
        (See Also-Student Records)
      - Task Force on Experiential and Developmental Programming, 1984 (Box 34)
      - Unit Committee
        - General, 1971 (Box 34)
        - Goal Statements, 1974 (Box 34)
        - Recommendations, 1974 (Box 34)
      - Year End Balances, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Student Voter Registration, 1974 (Box 34)
    - Substance Abuse
      (See Also-Alcohol, Drugs)
      - General, 1987-1988 (Box 34)
      - Peer Education Program, 1987 (Box 34)
      - Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
    - Tenants Union, 1970 (Box 34)
    - Testing of Human Subjects at the University, 1972 (Box 34)
    - Third World Peoples Conference, Proposal for, 1974 (Box 34)
    - Trans-Atlantic Charters, 1972-1973 (Box 34)
    - Undergraduate Admissions Task Force, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Undergraduate Initiatives (re:quality of undergraduate life and education), 1987-1988 (Box 34)
    - Undergraduate Library, 1984-1987 (Box 34)
    - University Activities Center (U.A.C.)
      - General, 1971-1985 (Box 34)
      - Budget/Funding (contains historical data), 1971-1985 (Box 34)
      - Constitution, 1977 (Box 34)
      - Events (includes some Michigan Union Opera and Musket schedules), 1974-1988 (Box 34)
      - Reports
        - Report of the University Activities Center Study Committee, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Report of the University Activities Center Study Committee, 1974 (Box 34)
      - Senior Officers, 1974 (Box 34)
      - Study Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 34)
    - University Cellar (Student Bookstore), 1986 (Box 34)
    - University Club, 1988 (Box 34)
    - University Facility Guidelines, 1974 (Box 34)
    - University Health Services
      - General, 1971-1989; 5 folders (Box 34)
      - Abortion Referrals Information, no date (Box 35)
      - Ad Hoc Study Group to Review Funding, 1976 (Box 35)
      - AIDS, 1985-1988 (Box 35)
      - Budget, 1985-1989 (Box 35)
      - Committee on Long Range Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
      - Goals, 1975-1977 (Box 35)
      - Malpractice Insurance, 1976 (Box 35)
      - Program Evaluation Committee, 1978 (Box 35)
      - Quality Assurance Committee, 1989 (Box 35)
      - Reports
        - Facility Report, circa 1980 (Box 35)
        - International Students and Health: Their Perceptions, Behaviors and Health Care Utilization, 1985 (Box 35)